A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor E. Lee Trinkle, 1919-1929 [bulk 1922-1926]
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Subject files, 1919-1929 [bulk 1922-1926]., Extent: 27.3 cu. ft. (78 boxes). (Box Boxes 1-78)
  - Mc, 1924-1926. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - McGuire, Stuart, 1922. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - M, 1922. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - M, 1923 January - June. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - M, 1923 July - December. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - M, 1924 January - March. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - M, 1924 April - December. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - M, 1925. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Manassas Battlefield Park, 1922-1925. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Mansion Inventory, Executive, 1922. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Markets, Division of, 1922. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Markets, Division of, 1922-1925. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Meade, Granville P., Will of, 1922-1925. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Medical College of Virginia (Richmond, Va.), 1922-1924. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Medical Examiner's Board, 1922-1923. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Medical Health Conference, 1925. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Memorials, 1922. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Mental Health, Commission, 1922. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Mental Hygiene, Governor's Advisory Board, 1922-1924. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Mineral Resources of Virginia, 1922-1925. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, Job requests and applications, 1922-1923. (Box 45, Folder 11-12)
  - Miscellaneous, Job requests and applications, 1923-1924. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, Job requests and applications, 1924-1925. (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
  - Monroe Centennial Celebration, 1923. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Monticello Association, 1923. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Monticello Association, 1923-1924. (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
  - Monticello Association, 1924. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Monticello Association, 1924. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Monticello Association, 1925. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Mortgage bonds, 1922. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Mother's Memorial, 1925. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1924. (Box 47, Folder 5-6)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1925. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Mount Airy trip, 1922. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Mount Vernon, Board of Visitors, 1922-1923. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Mount Vernon, Board of Visitors, 1924-1925. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - N, 1922. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - N, 1923-1924. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - N, 1924-1925. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - National Association for the Study of Feeblemindedness, 1924. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - National Cotton Conference, 1923. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - National Editorial Association, 1924. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - National Guard, 1922. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - National Guard, 1923-1924. (Box 48, Folder 7-8)
  - National Guard, 1924-1925. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - National Merchant Marine, 1923. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - National Parks, 1924-1925. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - National Parks, 1925. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - National Patriotic Council, 1925. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - National Prison Conference, 1922-1925. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - National Rivers and Harbor Congress, 1922-1923. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - National Rivers and Harbor Congress, 1923-1924. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - National Social Work Conference, 1923-1924. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - National State Parks Conference, 1922-1924. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - National Tax Association, 1924-1925. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - National Tuberculosis Association, 1924-1925. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - National Water Power Conference, 1922. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - National Wheat Conference, 1923. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Navy, Discharge from, 1922-1924. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Negro, National education Congress, 1923-1925. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - New Market trip, 1923. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers, Advertisement sent to, 1923. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper, Articles, 1924-1925. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper, Bonds, Extra session, 1923. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers, Subscriptions, 1921-1923. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers, Subscriptions, 1923-1925. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - New York Statues, 1921-1922. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1922-1925. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Normal School Board, 1924. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Notaries Public, 1922. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Notaries Public, 1922-1925. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Notaries Public, 1923-1925. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Notaries Public, 1925. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Nurses, State Board of Graduate, 1923-1925. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - O, 1922-1925. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Office Building, Virginia State, 1922. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Office Building, Virginia State, 1922. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Office Building, Virginia State, 1922-1923. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Office Building, Virginia State, 1922-1924. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Office Building, Virginia State, 1923. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Office Building, Virginia State, 1924. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Office Building, Virginia State, 1924-1925. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Optometry, State Board of, 1923-1925. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Oyster investigation, Commissioner of Fisheries, 1925. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - P, 1922. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - P, 1923. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - P, 1923. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - P, 1924. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - P, 1925. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Painting, 1924. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Pan American Commercial Congress, 1924. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Penitentiary, 1922-1923. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Penitentiary, 1922-1924. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Penitentiary, 1922-1926. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Penitentiary, Board of Directors, 1922-1925. (Box 54, Folder 6-7)
  - Penitentiary, Insane Convicts, 1922-1926. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Penitentiary, Road force, 1924-1925. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Penitentiary, State Farm, 1924. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Pensions, 1922-1923. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Pharmacy, State Board of, 1922-1925. (Box 55, Folder 2-3)
  - Politics, 1923-1924. (Box 55, Folder 4-5)
  - Politics, 1924. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Pollutions, 1922-1925. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Proclamations, 1922-1923. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Proclamations, 1922-1923. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Proclamations, 1923-1924. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Proclamations, 1924. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Proclamations, 1924-1925. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Proclamations, 1925. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Prohibition applications, 1921-1922. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Prohibition Dept., 1922-1923. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Prohibition Dept., 1924-1925. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1922. (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Programs, Ribbons and name tags, 1922-1923. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1923. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, Virginia Bureau of, 1922. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Public Health, 1923. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Public printing, 1922-1926. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Public Welfare, State Board of, 1922-1925. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Purchasing Agent, 1922. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Purchasing Agent, 1922. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Purchasing Agent, 1922. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Purchasing Agent, 1922-1925. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Q, 1922-1925. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - R, 1922. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - R, 1923. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - R, 1924. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - R, 1925. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate Board, 1924. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Recreation Congress, 1922. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Recreation Congress, 1922-1926. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Registered mail receipts, 1925. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Resolutions, Miscellaneous, 1922. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Rewards, 1922-1923. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Rewards, 1922-1925. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Rewards, 1923. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Richmond Chamber of Commerce, 1924-1925. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad, 1922-1924. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Rifle range transfer to Federal government, 1922-1923. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Round Table Conference, Mrs. Munford, 1922. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - S, 1922. (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - S, 1923. (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
  - S, 1923-1924. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - S, 1924. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - S, 1924-1925. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - S, 1925. (Box 60, Folder 8-9)
  - Sanitary Live Stock Board, 1922-1924. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Second Auditor, 1923. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1923-1924. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of the State, 1924-1925. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Sesquicentennial International Exposition, 1926. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Shell Fish Commissioner, 1922. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Sheppard Towner Act, 1921-1922. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Shirley, H.G., 1922-1923. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Smith, John, Capt., Portrait of, 1923-1925. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Smithey vs. Saunders, 1922-1925. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Social Work, Conference of, 1922. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Soldiers Home, R.E. Lee, 1924. (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - South Atlantic Coastal Highways Association, 1922-1925. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Southern Commercial Congress, 1922. (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Southern Commercial Congress, 1923-1925. (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Southern Exposition, 1924-1925. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Southern Exposition, 1924-1925. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Southern Forestry Congress, 1923-1925. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Southern Law and Order League, 1922. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Staff applications, 1921-1922. (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
  - Staff appointments, 1921-1922. (Box 62, Folder 7-8)
  - State Board of Education, 1922-1923. (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
  - State Board of Education, 1922-1924. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - State Board of Education, 1923-1924. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - State Board of Education, 1923-1925. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - State Board of Education, 1924-1925. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - State Board of Education, 1925. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - State Board of Education, Dockets, 1923-1926. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - State Board of Education, The Experimental Evaluation of Textbooks, undated. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - State Board of Health, 1922-1924. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - State Board of Health, 1924-1925. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1922. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1923. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1924. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1925-1926. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - State Departments, 1924-1925. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - State Depositories, 1922-1924. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - State Geologist, 1922-1923. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - State Geologist, 1924-1925. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - State Institutions, Special reports, 1923. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - State Institutions, Special reports, 1923. (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
  - State Library, 1922-1925. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - State Management Commission on Simplification in Government, 1922-1923. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - State Teachers College (Farmville, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - State Teachers College (Fredericksburg, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - State Teachers College (Harrisonburg, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - State Teachers College (Radford, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - State Treasurer, 1922-1925. (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - State Veterinarian, 1922-1924. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Statements by Governor, 1922-1924. (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Statements by Governor, 1922-1924. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Stone Mountain Memorial (Ga.), 1923-1924. (Box 67, Folder 2-3)
  - Stone Mountain Memorial (Ga.), 1923-1925. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Stone Mountain Memorial (Ga.), 1925. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Strikes, 1922. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Sulgrave Institution, 1924. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Accomack County, 1924-1925. (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Amherst County, 1925. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Appomattox County, 1925. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Arlington County, 1924-1925. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Bedford County, 1925. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Bland County, 1925. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Brunswick County, 1923-1924. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Buchanon County, 1922-1925. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Buckingham County, 1924-1925. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Carroll County, 1925. (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Charlotte County, 1925. (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Charlottesville, 1925. (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Chesterfield County, 1924. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Clarke and Frederick Counties, 1924-1925. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Craig County, 1925. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Culpeper County, 1924-1925. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Cumberland County, 1924. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Dinwiddie County, 1922-1923. (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Fairfax County, 1925. (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Fauquier County, 1923. (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Gloucester County, 1925. (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Goochland County, 1925. (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Grayson County, 1924-1925. (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Greene and Madison Counties, 1924-1925. (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Hanover County, 1925. (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Henry County, 1924. (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Isle of Wight County, 1922. (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, James City, Charles City, and New Kent Counties, 1924. (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Lee County, 1924-1925. (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Lunenburg County, 1925. (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Norfolk County, 1922. (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Orange County, 1925. (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Page County, 1925. (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Petersburg, 1923. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Princess Anne County, 1924-1925. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Prince William County, 1925. (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Rockingham County, 1925. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Southampton County, 1923. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Sussex County, 1925. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Washington County, 1925. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Wise County, 1925. (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Williamsburg, 1925. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Wythe County, 1922-1923. (Box 70, Folder 10-11)
  - Superintendent of Public Schools, Miscellaneous, 1922-1925. (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Swanson, Claude A., 1922. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - T, 1922-1923. (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - T, 1923. (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - T, 1923-1924. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - T, 1924. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - T, 1924-1925. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Tax Board, State, 1922-1924. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Tax Board, State, 1925-1926. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Tax Conference, 1922. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Tax Conference, 1923-1925. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Tax exempt securities, 1923-1925. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Tax on intangibles, 1924. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Tax sales, 1922-1923. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Tax suggestions, 1921-1922. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Tax suggestions, 1923-1924. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Tax suggestions, Dept. of Commerce press releases, 1923-1924. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Texas Cotton Palace Exposition, 1922-1923. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Tobacco Growers Co-operative Association, 1921-1925. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Trade Zone Bill, 1922. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Trinkle, E. Lee, Conference, 1922. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Trips, Letters, thanks, 1922-1923. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - U, 1922-1925. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - United States Good Roads Association, 1922-1923. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - United States Good Roads Association, 1923. (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
  - United States Good Roads Association, 1924. (Box 73, Folder 3-4)
  - United States Good Roads Association, 1925. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - United States Good Roads Association, 1925-1926. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - United States - Mexico Trade Conference, 1923. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - United States Naval Reserve, 1923-1925. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - University of Virginia, 1922-1925. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - University of Virginia, Board of Visitors, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - V, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Veterinarian, State, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Commission for the Blind, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Boys, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Girls, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Colored Boys, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Colored Girls, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Virginia- Maryland boundary line, 1927-1929. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1922-1925. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Military Institute, Board of Visitors, 1922-1924. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Military Institute, Hazing incident, 1924. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Military Institute, State cadet ships, 1922-1925. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute (Petersburg, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Normal School (Harrisonburg, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1922-1923. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1924-1926. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Board of Visitors, 1922-1924. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Extension Division,. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Real Estate Commission, 1924-1926. (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Virginia School for the Blind (Charlottesville, Va.), 1924-1925. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind (Staunton, Va.), 1922-1924. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, Colored (Newport News, Va.), 1922-1924. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1925. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, 1924. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Virginia War History Commission, 1924. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Vital Statistics, Bureau of, 1924-1925. (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Voting by mail, 1922-1924. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - W, 1922. (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - W, 1922-1923. (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - W, 1923. (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - W, 1924. (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - W, 1924-1925. (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - W, 1925. (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - War Memorial Commission, 1922-1925. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - War Memorial Commission, Program of a competition for the selection of architect and sculptor for War Memorial, 1925. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - War Trophy Distribution Board, 1922-1925. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Washington, George, 200th Anniversary, and Woodrow Wilson Memorial, 1925. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Water Power and Development Commission, 1924-1925. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Water Power and Development, North Carolina, 1925. (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Weights and Measurement Conference, 1922-1924. (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - west Point appointments, 1922-1925. (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - William and Mary, Board of Visitors, 1922-1925. (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Wilmington (De.), Launching of steamer State of Virginia, 1922. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, Foundation, 1925. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Workmen's compensation, 1922. (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Wrecks, Commissioners of, 1922-1923. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Y, 1922-1924. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Yorktown Manor Hotel and Country Club, 1923-1925. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Yorktown General Committee, 1922-1924. (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Yorktown General Committee, 1925-1926. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Yorktown National Council, 1922-1923. (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Z, 1923-1925. (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Series II: Extraditions, Pardons, and Prison Affairs, 1922-1926., Extent: 10.35 cu. ft. (23 boxes). (Box Boxes 79-101)
  Arranged into three subseries: Subseries A: Extraditions, Subseries B: Pardons, and Subseries C: Prison Affairs. Aranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Subseries A. Extraditions
    - Adison - Anderson (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Anglin - Austin (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Baker - Barrett (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Bartholomew - Baumgardner (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Beasley - Bell (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Benjamin, William A. (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Bennett - Bland (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Bobbitt - Boyd (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Bradley - Brinkley (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Brock - Bryson (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Bulk - Byrd (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Cable - Carroll (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Carson - Cauiess (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Chasom - Cluverius (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Coiner - Cox (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Craig - Curry (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - D'Abreu - Dixon (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Dodd - Duff (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - E (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax - Foster (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Francis - Furlong (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Gaber - Geer (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Gibbons - Gordon (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Grant - Gulbranson (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Hackney - Hanley (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Harding - Haynes (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Heath - Hinton (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Hobgood - House (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Howard - Hypes (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Ingersoll - Jeter (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Johnson - Judy (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Kabachnic - Ketland (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Kindel - Koneth (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Lacy - Lee (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Lender - Lyons (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Mc (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Macon - Marshall (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Marsland - Mayhugh (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Meadows - Merrill (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Michael - Mitchell (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Mobley - Moss (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Mullen - Myers (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Nance - Nyals (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Oakes - Ozmont (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Pace - Plasters (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Poenitzsch - Poyner (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Preller - Puffenberger (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Quinn - Reynolds (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Rhoton - Robinson (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Rochelle - Ruth (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Salasky - Sellers (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Shanks - Slaten (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Smith - Spruell (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Stafford - Stovall (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Stratides - Sykes (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Talbott - Terry (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Thomas - Tyson (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Ucker - Von Duhn (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Wade - Watts (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Weaver - Whitehead (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Wiggins - Willey (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Williams - Williamson (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Willis - Wright (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Xippas - Zoller (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B. Pardons
    - Abner - Akers (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Allen (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Alley - Andrade (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Appell - Aytes (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Bage - Barnes (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Barnett - Beazley (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Beck - Benton (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Berlind - Bishop (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Black - Blanchett (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Blanks - Bowen (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Bowers - Bradley (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Bradshaw - Broadus (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Brockenbrough - Brown (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Brummett - Byrd (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Cain - Cawthorn (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Chambers - Clayton (Box 90, Folder 1)